Obama! Obama!
Contrary to the rumors
that you've heard,
I was not born
in a manger.
I was actually born
on Krypton
and sent here
to save the planet Earth.
We cannot continue
to rely only on our military
in order to achieve
the national security objectives
that we've set.
Yes, we can.
Everybody somewhere
between the ages of 18 to 25
will serve three months
of basic training.
We've gotta have a civilian
National Security force
that's just as powerful,
just as strong.
Yes, we can!
Obama's healthcare plan
will include
coverage of all essential
medical services.
Yes, we can!
Obama is a cruel hoax.
He works for Wall Street.
He's an agent
of finance capital.
Where did you come up
with the number 700 billion dollars?
Here's the Treasury
spokeswoman's quote:
"It's not based on
any particular data point.
We just really wanted to come up
with a really big number."
To Democrats and Republicans
who've opposed this plan,
I say,
step up to the plate.
A few members
were even told
that there would be martial law
in America if we voted "no".
Secretary Henry Paulson
is no George Washington.
I don't think anyone questions,
Mr. Kashkari,
that you're working hard.
Our question is,
"Who are you working for?"
Obama pledged
that he would resume
the Security and Prosperity
Partnership talks
between Mexico and Canada
that President Bush initiated.
The old boss is starting
to look a lot like the new boss.
Robert Gates is gonna remain
on the job
as Defense Secretary
for at least a year.
Plenty of sources
knew about this meeting,
uh, told us
and others that
it was at Hillary Clinton's house,
but clearly it wasn't.
We've gotta give them a stake
in creating the kind of world order
that I think all of us
would like to see.
We see you causing a depression
so you can blow out the economy
and consolidate it
and bankrupt it.
We know that you are
enemies of free humanity
and we are here
standing against your tyranny.
The Obama Deception.
The truth strikes back.
Barack is like
the manager of Burger King.
All presidents are,
including Bush.
It's like this:
When your fries are cold,
if your burger's
not done right,
you go back to Burger King,
America,
or your government,
and you say,
"My burger's cold.
I want new fries."
First, you go to the cashier.
That's the courts.
You argue
to the courts.
The courts, if you can't get no justice
with the cashier, you say,
"Let me see the manager."
"I want to go
to the Supreme Court."
"I want
to see the President."
The manager comes out.
"Hi.
What can I do for you?"
Now the manager can override
the decisions of the cashier.
But you never get to see
the franchise owner of Burger King.
If you really have
a problem with your burger,
you need to go
see the franchise owner.
We need to go to the top,
or to the bottom.
We need to go to where
the real architecture of government is,
and it's not in a president.
It's in
a global scheme.
Politics in America today
is identical to pro-wrestling.
And what I mean
by that is,
in front of the cameras and
the public we all hate each other.
I'm gonna kick
my opponents butt.
I'm gonna wail him
from here to high water
and beat the crap out of him.
Yet behind the scenes
we all are friends going out to dinner.
- Going to dinner together.
- And, and, and...
It's all work.
- All intermarried.
- Show business.
It's showbiz.
And that's what you have
today in politics.
The Democrats and Republicans
aren't really opposed to each other.
Left and right mean nothing.
The only thing that counts is,
"Are you working
for Wall Street,
or are you trying to defend the people
against the financiers?"
It's pretty obvious that there's
some gigantic financial institutions
that have been pulling
the strings of politicians
in this country
for a long time.
And, just the fact that
we have it set up
where they can donate
millions of dollars
to these guys' funds,
these guys' campaigns...
I mean, how do we not
expect it all to go bad?
America in 2009
was desperate for change.
The past eight years
had been a disaster.
Those weapons of mass destruction
have gotta be somewhere.
Maybe under here?
George W. Bush,
who had claimed to be a conservative,
had tripled the size
of the Federal Government,
shredded the Constitution,
and destroyed the image
of the United States worldwide.
Nope,
no weapons over there.
Endless wars.
Over a million dead Iraqis.
And more than
five thousand dead US troops.
The Patriot Act.
Warrantless domestic wiretapping
and spying.
The end
of Posse Comitatus.
The rise of the treasonous
North American Union.
A deepening recession
sliding towards
total economic collapse.
These factors
and other abuses
had the American people
in a state of panic
for their future and the very existence
of the United States.
The elite
were in trouble.
The people were beginning
to see through their facade,
past their front man and
to the ruling elite behind the throne.
For the first time in US history,
both parties were universally hated.
Congress had
a 9% approval rating.
The globalist agenda
had stalled.
And then on to the scene came
a man who promised change,
change
we could all believe in.
Barack H. Obama promised to end the war
and bring our troops home fast.
He pledged
to uphold the Constitution
and to stop
the Federal Government
from spying
on the American people.
Candidate Obama
told American workers
that he was going to get them
out of NAFTA and GATT
and he's already
breaking those promises.
In this film,
we will prove
that Obama says one thing
and does another
and that he works for the very same
elite interest that Bush served.
The very interest
engineering the financial collapse
and formation of
a dictatorial world government.
This film is
not about left or right.
It is nonpartisan.
Our past documentary films are among
some of the most damning indictments
of George W. Bush and his administration
that have ever been made.
If humanity has any hope of
effecting real change for the better,
it will not come from
the Madison Avenue false-reality makers
who have cast Barak Obama
as the savior of the world.
To alter our course from tyranny to liberty,
to defeat the corrupt elite,
we must get
past the puppets
and confront the real
power structure of the planet.
Now we can see a new world
coming into view.
A world in which
there is the very real prospect
of a New World Order.
Webster Griffin Tarpley
is an accomplished geopolitical analyst
and historian.
Among his scholarly works
are the unauthorized biographies of
George Herbert Walker Bush
and Barack Hussein Obama.
Since Bush the Elder made his speech
at the United Nations
back in September of 1990
talking about the New World Order,
I think I've become
confused about
what's actually going on
in the world.
The New World Order
is a more palatable name
for the Anglo-American
World Empire.
It's the planetary domination
of London, New York,
Washington,
over the rest of the world.
It's hard to get people to join that
or think they have a part in it
if you call it
the Anglo-American World Empire.
If you call it the New World Order,
then people in India or
or someplace like that,
or the European Union might think,
"Well, there's something in that
for us too."
But that's not what it is.
It's the Anglo-American
New World Order.
It's really
the Old World Order.
It's the British Empire
morphing into the American Empire.
The US-British World Empire
is--is what you're gonna get.
Combines of powerful men
have always battled with each other
over the levers of power.
Gerald Celente
is recognized
as one of the world's
foremost trends forecasters
and is founder
of the Trends Research Institute.
People that are
knowledgeable know
that the fight that this country's
been waging since its inception,
is for the central bankers
not to take over the country.
And that's why people like
Andrew Jackson were elected.
And that's why people revere people like
Thomas Jefferson and others.
The takeover's happened
and it's a corporate takeover.
Agents of the Bank of England
attempted to assassinate
President Andrew Jackson
on multiple occasions
because of his resistance
against a private central bank
being set up in the United States.
And it was something
that Abraham Lincoln warned.
And this is, by the way,
why I believe he was assassinated.
This is
the Lincoln quote:
"The money powers prey upon
the nation in times of peace
and conspire against it
in times of adversity.
It is more despotic
than monarchy,
more insolent than autocracy,
more selfish than bureaucracy.
I see in the near future
a crisis approaching that unnerves me
and causes me to tremble
for the safety of my country.
Corporations
have been enthroned.
An era of corruption will follow
and the money power of the country
will endeavor
to prolong its reign
by working upon
the prejudices of the people
until the wealth is aggregated
in a few hands
and the Republic
is destroyed."
Wall Street
has killed Main Street.
So I know how unpopular it is
to be seen as helping banks right now,
especially when everyone is suffering
in part from their bad decisions.
I promise you,
I get it.
Up until about the Kennedy assassination
and the beginning of the war in Vietnam,
the United States is
a very powerful engine
for world progress.
It's the assassinations,
the Kennedy assassination,
and the others
in the 1960s,
the beginning
of the Vietnam war,
and the beginning of
the absolute domination
of the Wall Street group
over every other interest.
Nobody else counts except
the Wall Street money masters.
That has now made
the United States into,
uh, no longer
a force for progress,
but something
very different.
Often a force for
destruction in the world.
The Military Industrial Complex
has taken over the country
along with the Wall Street gang.
If you look also
at the people
that Obama has put on
his appointments list,
it's all Wall Street.
It's government of Wall Street,
by Wall Street,
and for Wall Street.
There's nobody from heavy industry,
there's nobody from the auto sector,
nobody from Silicon Valley,
nobody from big oil,
nobody from defense,
no labor,
no women, no retirees,
no small business, nothing!
It's pure Wall Street.
The only people who have
a voice in Obama's counsels
are Wall Street finance oligarchs.
That's all there is.
Nobody else counts
for anything under Obama.
It's the most extreme
Wall Street administration
we've ever had.
Before his death,
President Woodrow Wilson
apologized to the public
regretting that
he had been deceived
by a group
of international bankers
and the country's financial system
had fallen into their iron grip
via the
Federal Reserve Act of 1913.
Whether sought or unsought,
by the Military Industrial Complex,
the potential for the disastrous rise
of misplaced power exists
and will persist.
Dwight D. Eisenhower.
He warned the people
that the Military Industrial Complex
was taking over the country.
Only three years
after leaving office,
President Eisenhower's
prophetic warning
concerning the threat posed
to our system of government
by the Military Industrial Complex
came to pass.
President John F. Kennedy
had enraged the entire elite network.
Now Kennedy was brought in as somebody
who was expected to be a puppet.
It was thought that his pro-Nazi father,
Joseph P. Kennedy,
the bootlegger,
the speculator,
would guarantee that Kennedy
would be obedient to the establishment.
They thought that
Kennedy was a sex maniac
who could be manipulated
through all of this,
but it turned out that
through his personal suffering,
Kennedy had discovered
a personal sense of himself
which went beyond
just being a puppet
and he began to think
about things like economic recovery,
world peace,
having a space program,
making deals
with the Soviets,
cutting the Federal Reserve
down to size,
and a whole series of other things.
Executive Order number 11110,
signed by President Kennedy,
began the process of abolishing
the private Federal Reserve.
Kennedy was also pushing
for real civil rights reform
and had begun the process
of pulling the troops out of Vietnam.
The last time you had
an actual president was Kennedy.
The oligarchs took
swift and decisive action.
When John Kennedy attempted
to take the government back
from the robber barons,
he was brutally murdered.
The message to future US presidents
and leaders across the world was clear,
"Do as you're told
or die."
John Fitzgerald Kennedy
was the last true president
of the United States,
and until the globalists
are removed from power,
we will never have
another real one.
The other thing about
the American presidency,
you've got to remember,
is that this is a puppet post.
It's automatically
gonna be a puppet post.
The idea that Obama
is somebody
who's gonna come in
and exercise real authority,
when he's obviously been chosen
and given everything
that he's got
by these financiers?
Presidents are now little
more than corporate pitchmen
who take
all the political heat
while the controllers
remain in the shadows,
safe from public scrutiny.
Hip-hop icon
KRS One
is not just known
for selling millions of albums.
He has led a tireless crusade
against youth violence
and has been a strong voice
for human rights.
If they controlled it before,
what are you...?
Why don't...?
What makes you think
they're not controlling it now?
The country was
on the verge of revolution.
They threw
a black man up.
Now we're like this.
They give him the money.
They give him the bundling.
They give him vote fraud.
They give him
the media whores.
They give him goons.
They even have elected officials
making threats to put people in jail
if they criticize Obama
in public.
All this is the mark of a puppet, uh,
and that means that he is a puppet.
Actually, more of a puppet
than anybody else.
More than a puppet
than Mrs. Clinton would have been.
Even more of a puppet
than--than McCain.
He's the maximum puppet that we've had,
certainly since, since Jimmy Carter.
They put a black face
on the New World Order,
and now
we all happy.
KRS ain't buying it.
In the real executive
power structure,
the president serves
the Military Industrial Complex,
itself owned
by the international bankers.
If there's a revolution,
the population just throws out
the Prime Minister or President.
The elite
stays in power,
because the public is never aware
of who the real enemy is.
In Evian, France, in 1991,
standing before the Bilderberg Group,
the apex of the world government
power structure,
David Rockefeller
defined the New World Order
as a system
of world government
serving
the international banking elite.
For decades, the banker-owned media
would attack anyone
who dared
to warn the public
that a dictatorial
world government
was being constructed
right under their nose,
and that national sovereignty
was being deliberately destroyed.
And now,
after years of denial,
the media and the elite
themselves
are proudly announcing
that not only is world government real,
but it is the answer
to the financial crisis
that they carefully engineered.
Suddenly,
the Wall Street Journal tells us
that the North American Union
is here
and that getting rid of the dollar
for a common currency
with Canada and Mexico
is good?
The Financial Times of London,
published by a member
of the Bilderberg Group,
crowed that a dictatorial
world government
had been kept in the shadows
for our own good
and that it was now time
for it to emerge
from behind the curtains
of national security.
White House Chief of Staff,
Rahm Emanuel, stated on record
that they can't let
this crisis go to waste.
You never want
a serious crisis to go to waste.
But what I mean by that:
It's an opportunity to do things
that you think
you could not do before.
And Henry Kissinger,
who gave Barack Obama
his first job
out of college,
told national television
that the economic collapse
was a great opportunity
to bring in
the New World Order.
He went on to say that
Barack Obama
was the perfect person
to sell it to the world.
...but he can give a new impetus
to American foreign policy,
partly because the reception of him
is so extraordinary around the world.
I think his task will be
to develop an overall strategy
for America,
in this period,
when really,
a New World Order can be created.
It's a great opportunity.
It isn't just a crisis.
In June of 2006, our team traveled
to Ottawa, Canada
to gather intelligence
on the Shadow Government's agenda
for the coming years.
- I think that's the Queen.
- It is.
It's the Queen!
Investigative journalist
and best-selling author, Daniel Estelin,
had been tracking the Bilderberg Group
for more than 16 years.
His moles inside Bilderberg
informed him
that the elite were planning
to first run the price of gas up,
to $150 a barrel,
unimaginable in 2006.
He also reported that
after suckering the middle class
back into the stock market,
the group was going to implode
the sub-prime mortgage market
and destroy public confidence.
Well, one of the things that, you know,
we're getting from this morning's...
this afternoon's conference...
this morning's conference,
was about the, uh,
the--the energy crisis, the price of oil.
This, the afternoon conference,
which started about 4 o'clock,
4:00 or 4:30...
They were talking about, uh...
One of the American delegates
(I--I wasn't told
who exactly it was)
was talking
about the, uh,
the concern that
the American citizens have had
with the, you know,
with the housing prices going down.
So they're not investing
that money.
So what they needed
to do is
they needed to create the illusion
that everything is going well.
So what they're going to do
over the next year, year and a half,
is to bring the market
back up to 1998-1999 levels.
They're gonna get
all the suckers to invest
whatever little money
they have left over,
and that's when they're going
to make the economy bottom drop out.
They need to destroy
the economy because,
as we're running out of oil,
when people don't travel
(at least that's what they're saying),
when people don't travel,
when people don't have money
they don't travel,
they don't spend
any money,
which means you don't waste
a lot of oil and natural gas.
- That's the afternoon scheduled session.
- So how does this source,
I mean just ball park, I mean...
So, you have this source. Is it...?
Well, actually,
there are two people, uh,
who are members
of the Bilderberg Club
It's actual members that are...
They are members
of the Bilderberg Club who,
for years
and years and years,
have been going and participating
in all the conversations.
They have always been
dead-on, always.
And last year, they said
the oil prices are gonna go up to $150.
At the time it was $39.
It went up to $76; basically doubled.
If it doubles again, it's gonna be back
to where these people say
- it is going...
- If they attack Iran, it will hit 150.
Year after year,
Estelin and other reporters
like Jim Tucker,
are able to report
on future events
with stunning accuracy
all because they know the agenda
of the Bilderberg Group.
The Bilderberg Group sits at
the top of the world power structure.
125 of the richest
and most influential individuals
on the globe
make up its membership.
From Istanbul, Turkey,
to Chantilly, Virginia,
we have tracked
the elusive Bilderberg Group.
Bilderberg always insists
on a media blackout.
By June of 2008,
we had already figured out
that Barack Obama
was the elites' puppet of choice.
The national media
claimed
that during the weekend
the Bilderberg Group
was scheduled to meet
that Obama had speaking engagements
set for Chicago
and the Midwest.
We knew better.
In a classic
bait-and-switch,
the Obama Campaign
told the press corp
to get on
Obama's campaign plane
and that Obama would join them
on the flight to Chicago.
Campaign staff
then slammed the door shut.
The fawning press
had been shanghaied
as Obama's campaign aircraft
lifted off without Obama.
Robert, why were we not told
about this meeting
and that the Senator
wouldn't be on our plane
until the doors were shut
and we were about to taxi to take-off?
Again, uh...
We had a desire...
Senator Obama had a desire
to do some meetings.
Others have the desire
to meet with him tonight
in a private way
and that's what we're doing.
We set up
these meetings...
They're being,
they're being done tonight.
Again, I'm...
I...
Is there more than one meeting?
Is there more than one person
with whom he is...
I'm not gonna get into
all the details of the meetings.
I don't know
that I've got a ton more
different answers
for all of your questions.
Obama wasn't going
to Chicago.
He had a meeting
to attend.
A secret meeting.
Initially, it was believed
that the secret meeting
took place at
Clinton's Washington DC home.
Obama's spokesman
denied that
but won't confirm
where the former rivals met.
He also declined to comment
on their topics of discussion.
For a day and a half,
the mainstream media
engaged in a wild goose chase
trying to find out
where Hillary and Obama had gone.
Three cover stories later,
the corporate press had to admit,
they had no idea
where the two candidates had gone.
And to this day,
Clinton and Obama aren't talking.
Plenty of sources
knew about this meeting,
uh, told us
and others
that it was at Hillary Clinton's house,
but clearly it wasn't.
In 2008, the trail led us
to the Westfields Marriott Hotel,
right outside
Washington, DC.
We just flew into
We're driving
to the Westfields Marriott.
Tomorrow, the hotel's closed
throughout the week
into the weekend
for the Bilderberg Group meeting.
We're gonna check in
the night before.
They're gonna
kick us out tomorrow.
So, we're going directly into
the belly of the beast.
The hotel will be filled with
at least five spy agencies:
CIA, Defense Intelligence, Mossad, um...
European Union Security.
We checked in to the Westfields Marriott
48 hours before hotel guests
were scheduled to be thrown out
ahead of the annual meeting.
The building was nestled in the heart
of the Military Industrial Complex
with the National Reconnaissance Office
and Raytheon,
just a stone's throw away.
The plan tonight is
to try to not get arrested,
dodge the security,
get in there,
get some--some footage of the elite
arriving in the morning
because some arrive before
they officially lock it down,
and then getting
out of the building.
That's our plan.
I'm also gonna be, um,
getting a call
by a international
syndicated radio show,
Coast To Coast AM
with George Noory.
And, all week, he's getting
briefings from me every night,
uh, about things
as they develop.
George,
we're sitting here in the room.
As the phone rings
with your producer Tom Danheiser
to put me on,
the fire alarm goes off.
So everybody
is exiting the building.
I know
this is a setup.
They timed it
exactly when this happened.
Open the door.
I want them
to hear the fire alarm.
Open the door.
I want people to hear this live...
to the 16 million people listening.
George,
do you hear that?
Now, now, now,
they're gonna use this as an excuse.
The Westfields Marriott
right outside DC in Chantilly.
They want to use this
to flush us outta here.
They are very upset.
Everybody
that covers Bilderberg
was detained two years ago,
interrogated, screamed at.
They said Bilderberg was upset about me,
wanted to stop us.
This is guaranteed.
Everywhere we go,
we're followed.
We have another hotel across town
as a base of operations.
They were there, questioning us,
getting in our faces.
We're being followed everywhere.
I need everybody's support
right now.
I pray to God
they don't try to set me up.
They may have tried to concoct this
in some way to say,
you know, look, they didn't
leave during a fire drill,
assessing me, knowing I would
stay and do the interview.
But again, the moment
the phone rang with Tom Danheiser,
the moment the phone rang,
the guys answered it.
I'm standing there.
The alarm goes off.
It's going off right now.
The guests are exiting
the hotel out there.
Of course,
there's no fire.
This is just absolutely insane.
I noticed, too, that there was over
a hundred security people here today,
but tonight we got back
and it was a total ghost town.
And this is what's insane:
We have a security guy
walk up to us 30 minutes ago,
about 25 minutes ago,
before this happened,
and said,
"What are you guys doing?"
We said, "We're just walking around
checking out the artwork in the hotel,"
which we actually
were admiring and,
but we were also going
around getting some footage.
And, you know, they said,
"Well, no cameras allowed."
We said, "Fine."
And then he said,
"Yeah, we had somebody
do a fire alarm a few weeks ago."
And me and Rob,
my camera guy, we're going,
"Why is he telling us
about a fire alarm?"
I forgot that part,
George.
These bastards
have done this.
I don't know how.
They're planning to try
to set us up or something.
But this is incredible.
We are here in the middle of this
right now, George.
Stay there.
Keep it locked.
Let's go.
Let's get
out of here now, Richard.
Don't screw around anymore.
We got out of here
at exactly the right time.
- Is this the way out?
- Yeah.
Yeah, we got
a car right behind us.
We made about, what,
five turns
and the sixth turn,
the same car's following us?
And now it looks like
he's following us into a...
He came out of
Bilderberg.
the Westfields.
He's being
a little bit subtle but...
Not too...
There he is.
- That's him over there in the blue car.
- that green, ah... yeah.
Yeah.
We're headed back
to the Marriott here
in Chantilly, Virginia,
the scene of Bilderberg 2008.
We've successfully infiltrated
the last day and a half inside.
Got out
with some great stuff.
We've been tailed.
And now
we're going back to...
cover the dignitaries,
the elitists, as they arrive.
And right now
is the prime time for them
to start arriving
for the next 3 or 4 hours.
We took about
a 30 minute break.
I'm sure we missed a few
but it doesn't matter,
because we've got scores of people
that just organically are listeners,
Infowarriors that are out here
taking action.
Yeah!
And we're gonna be out here
for the next three days
while you try to chart
the future of our destiny.
We're taking
our destiny back!
You're not our gods
or our masters!
We witnessed at least seven convoys
of armed Secret Service entering
the Westfields Marriott
and internal sources confirmed
that both candidates did attend at least
one meeting inside the conference.
While the Bilderberg Group
was 100% successful in 2008
at keeping their name
out of the mainstream media,
they did not fare
as well
when it came to
the exploding independent press.
During the entire two day event,
anti-New World Order protesters
and alternative media
encircled the hotel.
You are being exposed
everywhere!
From David Rockefeller!
From John Edwards!
From Bill Clinton!
Your game of secrecy
is over!
...you piece of filth!
You piece of trash!
There's Bernanke, man!
Bernanke,
you're going down!
Obama,
we know you're here, Obama!
You cleared your schedule
for the next three days!
We know
you're in Virginia!
Arch-criminals!
New World Order scum!
We are not your slaves,
you scum!
Brave Americans came from
all over the United States
and bullhorned the main conference hall
at close range
as the global power brokers
schemed inside.
Freedom!
You are criminals!
You control
the central banks!
You control the currency!
And you're turning our beautiful
country and world into a nightmare!
The global elite
are desperate
to keep their organizational
meetings a secret.
They are keenly aware
that if the population
discovers that policy is being
developed covertly
by powerful special interests,
the people will revolt.
It is our duty
to expose these criminals.
It's a criminal act
under federal law
for federal officials
to have private meetings
to discuss world policy, uh,
with non-federal workers.
So everybody from the State Department,
Treasury Department, White House,
Defense Department
and others who show up,
as they always do...
They're committing a criminal act
simply by being here
to attend a secret meeting
with officials from other countries
to--to discuss US policy
in the world.
So, literally, it's a criminal act
and every newspaper, every broadcaster,
has a patriotic duty
to expose these scum
and the, uh,
evil they project.
The election primaries served
as a great diversion
while the true future course
of the nation
was being set
behind closed doors.
You've got, obviously,
the Bilderberg Group founded by
the former Nazi, uh,
Prince Bernard of Holland.
You've got
the Trilateral Commission,
founded by David Rockefeller's
Zbigniew Brzezinski.
They're the ones who ran
the Carter Administration.
Everybody in
the Carter administration,
from Carter and Mondale
and Volker and Brzezinski,
were all members
of the Trilateral Commission.
Founding member of rap sensation
Public Enemy, Professor Griff,
gave us his view
of the Obama phenomenon.
Barack Obama's been given a pass
by the bluebloods.
He's been given the okay
by certain secret societies
for them
to let him in.
I truly believe, um, imperialism
and fascism needs a facelift.
And the facelift
is gonna have to be black.
And the--the reason
why I believe that?
It's simply because, um...
I think they're trying
to go into Africa.
Well, they're already
in Africa,
but they want to totally control
all the natural minerals
that they're going to need
to carry themselves
into the 21st,
22nd and 23rd centuries.
Are you following me?
So, I think they have to go through
a phase of galvanizing
the masses of dark-skinned people.
They truly believe
that change needs to come,
but the change
that they are talking about
is not necessarily change for the better
as far as the masses of the people.
It's probably
a better change for them.
It's not gonna change for us,
the little man on the totem pole.
And no one
looks at the agenda.
- No one looks at the agenda.
- As long as he positions himself right,
have the right tie on,
have the right smile,
repeats the slogans
over and over,
and drives it, and drives it home,
the average, the average American
is just gonna swallow it
hook, line and sinker.
And we don't even know
what the agenda is.
Writing in his 1964 book,
With No Apologies,
Senator Barry Goldwater
said,
"The Trilateral Commission
is intended to be
the vehicle
for multinational consolidation
of the commercial and
banking interests by seizing control
of the political government
of the United States.
"The Trilateral Commission represents
a skillful, coordinated effort
to seize control and consolidate
the four centers of power:
political, monetary,
intellectual and ecclesiastical.
What the Trilateral Commission intends,
is to create a worldwide economic power
superior to the political governments
of the nation-states involved.
As managers and creators of the system,
they will rule the future.
Bilderberg issues executive decisions
and prime directives
to its sub-directorates
for implementation.
The Trilateral Commission takes
the Bilderberg Group agenda
and executes it
through regional roundtable groups
throughout Europe,
Asia and the Americas.
The Council on Foreign Relations
serves as the managing roundtable group
in the United States sector.
The Council on Foreign Relations
has dominated every administration
since the days of FDR.
The way in which
they make policy and rule
is that they are a
polycentric, oligarchical system.
You have to be
a finance oligarch.
Remember, this is not a society
ruled by generals, not by priests,
not by bureaucrats, not by demagogues,
none of those, but by bankers.
Bankers rule, and the bankers
set up these institutions.
They set up things
modeled on the Royal Institute
for International Affairs,
Chatham House,
and the Milner Roundtable
of the period
right after the Boer War.
So even
before World War I,
you had the British
setting up these roundtables,
institutes, with publications
and conferences.
And this is
how they make policy.
Upon Obama's inauguration,
members of the Bilderberg Group,
Trilateral Commission and CFR,
flooded into
every position of power
in the Executive Branch,
replacing Trilateral Commission
and CFR members,
who previously filled the positions
during
the Bush administration.
When you look at the, uh,
US ruling class,
you'd have to say
that they're a really pathetic bunch
of failures and bunglers.
They are a miserable excuse
for a ruling class.
And that's one of
the big problems we have,
is you go from Clinton
to Bush to Obama.
What stays the same is the ruling elite
that gives these puppets
the orders
that they act on,
and these orders are wrong-headed,
let's say, to say the least.
They are basically bankrupt.
They're gonna to lead
to the collapse of this civilization.
What they're doing is using
the existence of the United States
as a formerly
powerful nation-state
to act out
their Wall Street fantasies
of world of domination
and maintaining their capital structures
and maintaining their system of looting
and this can't be done.
So, the basic question is:
They've hijacked our country
and you've got
to take it back from them.
You've got to drive Wall Street
out of the government
and at that point,
you have a reasonable chance
of getting back
to prosperity
and some kind of peace and order
in international affairs.
We had a chance to speak with
economist and author George Humphrey.
They have created
a power elite.
And we're not talking about your...
the--the millionaire down the street.
You can't even be
a member of their club
unless you're
a multi-billionaire.
And friends, this is not about
rich versus poor.
This is about
a very, very small handful
of--of the worst criminal element
on this planet
manipulating and destroying
the good people of this nation
and of this world.
About this Obama, with change,
look at the people he's put in
to mastermind
the economic recovery.
Larry Summers.
I love it!
Every time they talk about
Larry Summers,
he's always brilliant.
He's another brilliant one.
He's the one that helped
dismantle the Glass-Steagall Act,
the banking act that was
put in place in the 1930s
so the banks couldn't get... become
the banksters that they've become.
In the 1990s, you had
the beginning of the derivatives bubble,
thanks to people like
Alan Greenspan, Rubin, Summers;
a lot of the people who are now back
in the Obama administration.
And the derivatives,
I think,
are the centerpiece
of this entire problem today.
These are
the same people:
Geithner,
from the Treasury Department.
Can you imagine that?
Now we have
the US Treasury Secretary,
who also is
a Robert Rubin protg
of the Larry Summers group
that dismantled Glass-Steagall
and--and broke apart
the regulations
that would have prohibited
the banks and brokerages
from becoming these criminals.
He was the former President
of the New York Federal Reserve?
And now
he's our Treasury Secretary?
As we all know, the Federal Reserve
is as federal as Federal Express.
It's a private bank.
And now we've put
this guy in charge of it?
I mean can't we...?
Wall Street has hijacked Washington
in broad daylight.
Every single one of his appointments
support the status quo.
Every one of his appointments
are there to screw the American people.
Every single one of his appointments
are people who are working
to bring down the Republic
and the Constitution of this country.
Secretary of the Treasury,
Timothy Geithner:
Bilderberg Group and
Trilateral Commission member.
Secretary of State, Hillary Clinton
is a Bilderberg and CFR member.
She is also married to
Trilateral Commission member,
William Jefferson Clinton.
Ambassador to the United Nations,
Susan Rice:
Trilateral Commission.
National Security Adviser,
General James L. Jones:
Bilderberg,
Trilateral Commission and CFR.
Deputy National Security Adviser,
Thomas Donilon:
Trilateral Commission, CFR.
Special State Department Envoy,
Henry Kissinger:
Bilderberg Group,
Trilateral Commission and CFR.
Chairman, Economic Recovery Committee,
Paul Volcker:
Bilderberg Group,
Trilateral Commission,
Council on Foreign Relations.
The Director of National Intelligence,
Admiral Dennis C. Blair:
Bilderberg Group,
Trilateral Commission, CFR.
Secretary of Defense,
Robert Gates:
Bilderberg Group,
Trilateral Commission, CFR.
Deputy Secretary of State,
James Steinberg:
Bilderberg Group,
Trilateral Commission, CFR.
State Department Special Envoy,
Richard Haas:
Bilderberg Group, Trilateral Commission,
and President of the CFR
Obama Presidential Adviser,
Alan Greenspan:
Bilderberg Group,
Trilateral Commission, CFR.
State Department Special Envoy,
Richard C. Holbrooke:
Bilderberg,
Trilateral, CFR.
And the list goes
on and on.
Even if Barack Obama were the most
wonderful person in the world,
he was groomed
and brought to power
by the global elite
to carry out their agenda.
Humanity must look
past Obama
and realize that
presidents come and go,
but the Shadow Government
and their program
of global enslavement continues.
How could people be
so stupid and gullible
to believe
a bunch of political people.
So people
who voted for Obama
were trying to express I think,
first of all, something worthwhile:
their hatred for Bush,
Cheney, the neocons,
the desire to punish the Republicans
for their adventures,
their police state,
and their economic depression.
The second question was,
on the economy,
people felt that Bush was
selling them down the river
into a world depression.
He is, of course, the new
Herbert Hoover in that regard,
so they were trying to get
something different from that.
The tragedy,
of course, is
(and this is really why Obama
was groomed and prepared
over a period
of almost 30 years now)
that Obama is there to frustrate
and to deceive all of those hopes.
Obama is a cruel hoax.
He's a bogus sham.
He's an absolute denial
of everything
that you'd expect from
an American president.
It is very disturbing
to see well-meaning people
falling for high tech propaganda
over and over again.
It happened after 9/11.
The American people en masse
were swept into a mob psychology,
irrationally throwing
their common sense to the wind
and doing whatever
the administration told them to.
The general public eventually caught
on to the fact
that George W. Bush
was a deceitful thug
and that the economy
was in freefall.
In the midst of it all,
Barack Obama was there
speaking out against
the abuse of the people
at the hands
of the establishment.
With the election of Barack Obama,
the world rejoiced
that the United States was no longer
in the hands of mad men.
But unfortunately for humanity,
this was another vicious fraud.
I want to like the guy.
He speaks gently.
He's intelligent.
He is...
He seems to be a man of peace.
He is just as charismatic
as they come.
But you know what:
is that a tree is really, really
measured by the quality of its fruit.
And when you, kind of,
put away all the flowery words,
when you put away
all the rhetoric,
all the rock and roll music,
what he does is what's important
for the people of this country,
starting with the truth.
Obama is
notoriously a liar.
He promised that
he would get out of Iraq,
I think, within
16 months at some point.
We had Samantha Power
telling The Scotsman
that he wouldn't be bound
by those promises
and sure enough, he's now not
gonna be bound by those promises.
Obama pledged in hundreds
of speeches and interviews
that within six months
of being elected,
he was going to bring
our troops home from Iraq.
But after he was inaugurated,
the story changed.
Now he said
that they would "look"
at bringing "some" of the troops
home in 16 months.
Two weeks later,
his story had changed again.
Now the administration
would "look"
at bringing the troops home
in 23 months.
Well,
Obama's already fudging.
He has fudged since day one
in this election
to where he first said,
we're getting out.
Well, now it's a timetable
and now it's da, da, da.
'Cause they're getting
to him.
They're understanding
that he ain't gonna be able
to get them out because
people more powerful than him got us in.
When he first ran, remember,
he was gonna take the troops out.
I get in there...
Troops come home, day one.
There is no military solution in Iraq
and there never was.
I will begin to remove our troops
from Iraq immediately.
And then that went to
16 months.
And now he's going to add,
they're saying,
another 30,000,
or more troops to Afghanistan.
Next, he sent 30,000
more Marines to Afghanistan,
doubling the total number of forces
in the crosshairs.
Barack then announced
that he was going to move
missile systems into Eastern Europe
to encircle Russia.
But after all,
what should we expect,
after he kept Bush's
Secretary of Defense Robert Gates?
The outcome
of this policy is
if you're constantly meddling
near the Russian borders
with these fascist creeps,
IMF-NATO agents like
Yushchenko of Ukraine,
or Sakashvilli of Georgia,
or these Kachinsky twins in Poland,
or various collections of people
in Latvia, Lithuania, Estonia,
you're tied to these gangsters
and if they decide to start a war,
that rapidly escalates
into thermonuclear World War III.
This is worse
than the neocons.
Bush and Cheney
never got as far
as Brzezinski, Soros and
the other people running Obama.
Barack Obama swore that he would
vote to repeal the Patriot Act,
but then he voted
for it's reauthorization.
Obama decried
the Bush administration's
illegal warrantless wiretapping
of the American people.
Then he voted
to legalize it.
Obama pledged
that he would filibuster
any attempt
to give retroactive immunity
to the telephone companies,
the telecom companies.
Except, he then turned around
and voted for that bill.
Most people don't know,
for example,
that he voted
to reinstate the Patriot Act
and more
government wiretapping.
Candidate Obama told
desperate factory workers
in speech after speech
that he was going
to renegotiate NAFTA and GATT
to make it more fair
for American workers.
It is absolutely true
that NAFTA was a mistake.
But then his campaign was caught
sending out memos
to top corporate leaders,
telling them not to worry
and that it was just campaign rhetoric.
We had Obama saying,
"You know, I'm against free trade."
"I don't like NAFTA
and all those free trade sellouts."
We had Austin Goldsby
going to the Canadian diplomats
and saying,
"Don't, don't mind him.
He's just popping off.
That's just election era rhetoric.
It doesn't mean anything."
Presidential candidate Barack Obama
was publicly criticizing
the North American Free Trade Agreement
in a bid for votes,
but privately telling Canadian officials
not to worry about it.
He said that he was going
to bring us peace in the Middle East.
He said that
he was going to bring us
transparency
and a balanced economy.
He said that he was going
to not have, have lobbyists.
He said he was going
to clean up government.
to work for the environment.
And point, by point,
by point,
within the first month
of his inauguration,
he has lied, and deceived,
and cheated the American people.
The people of the United States
and the world were filled with hope
that Obama was the real deal,
when in his first week in office,
he signed
an executive order
supposedly closing Guantanamo Bay
and other secret prisons.
Then the press actually had a chance
to read the executive order
and were shocked to find
that the executive order only said
that Obama was thinking about
closing Guantanamo in a year.
But worst of all,
the executive order continued
the practice of rendition,
which the LA Times called,
secret abductions.
They don't know.
They think that he signed off
immediately on closing Guantanamo,
but he's allowing prisoners now
to be taken to foreign countries,
and not knowing where
they're sending them,
and to be tortured
in foreign countries.
They don't know that
they kept that provision in there.
Obama is now continuing the practice
of secret arrest, secret prisons,
and most importantly,
indefinite detention without trial.
When a British high court
said that
it was preparing to release secret
British and US torture orders
that prove that the Bush administration
was ordering personnel
to systematically abuse
detainees,
Barack Obama threatened to cut
of all US intelligence ties to England.
To add
insult to injury,
he stated that the program
was important to national security,
not only endorsing Bush's crimes,
but continuing them.
Obama voted for reinstatement
of the Patriot Act
and by his early deeds already again,
as we saw with his...
the issues of retention,
he's willing to send people
that have been charged
with nothing
to be tortured to, so-called,
get the truth out of them.
If the makers of this film attempted
to cover all of Obama's lies,
this documentary
would never be released
because there are new ones
every day.
So, in the interest of time,
we're going to cover one more big one.
Barack and his handlers
made the cornerstone of his campaign,
keeping lobbyists and donors
out of his administration.
Within hours of being elected,
Obama did a 180
and filled the White House
and Federal Government
with lobbyists and donors
at all levels.
Obama picked William Lynn,
the top lobbyist for Raytheon,
to fill the number two position
of the Department of Defense.
Timothy Geithner,
former president of the private
Federal Reserve Bank of New York,
was picked by Obama
to be Secretary of the Treasury.
Geithner promptly crammed
the Treasury Department
full of lobbyists like his
Chief of Staff, Mark Patterson,
formerly the top lobbyist
at Goldman Sachs.
Obama appointed top lobbyist
to the Saudi Royal Family,
George Mitchell,
as the lead
Middle Eastern envoy.
Obama appointed the king
of Wall Street lobbyists,
Leon Panetta,
to head up the CIA.
Obama tapped Tom Daschle,
top lobbyist for healthcare firms,
to run the Department of Health
and Human Services.
And the list goes
on and on.
Then, three weeks
into his administration,
Obama launched a new lie,
more outrageous than the previous.
With Academy Award-level conviction,
he said that he was upset
about the banker bailout which
his own Chief of Staff, Rahm Emanuel,
another former Wall Street executive,
had engineered.
Obama said that he had signed
an executive order
capping the CEO salaries of those
who had taken the bailout money.
There was just
two problems:
All the major banks and
brokerage firms were exempt,
and the new order only dealt
with any future bailouts,
and those were to be
on the honor system.
What gets people upset,
and rightfully so,
are executives
being rewarded for failure.
AIG, Bank of America, and CitiGroup,
which have received billions
in bailout money
don't fall under this plan.
Only banks negotiating future agreements
with the government will be restricted.
But this appears to be built
on an honor system,
and White House Press Secretary,
Robert Gibbs,
had a hard time explaining
how enforcement would work.
Well, let, let,
let me get...
I--I will get clarification
from Treasury on that.
Generally speaking,
this is already the biggest liar
and the biggest disappointment
that we've seen in recent history.
And again, qualitatively
beyond the rather low standard set
by Bush the Elder and Clinton,
in terms of delivering on promises.
Bottom line:
Obama is a fantastic actor
and an even better liar.
His track record
is clear.
He has done the opposite of everything
he told the people he would do.
They'll make up
one lie after another.
And if you believe these people,
knock yourself out.
I don't believe
a word they say.
Within one month of the passage
of the first banker bailout bill,
the press reported that
over five trillion dollars
had just disappeared
out of the US Treasury.
By December, the amount of money
that had been stolen
had reached
$8.5 trillion.
The leadership
of both political parties
circled the wagons
and would not discuss
where the money
had gone.
End the Fed! End the Fed!
Informed Americans protested
the private Federal Reserve System
at all 38 of their regional
governorship offices.
Arrest
Bernanke and Paulson!
Arrest all the criminals
that stole the banker bailout money!
Yeah! Yeah!
It was refreshing
to see people standing up
against
the real power structure,
not being distracted
by the elite's front men like
George W. Bush
and Barack Obama.
We traveled
to Dallas, Texas,
to cover "We, the people,"
taking on the real enemy.
Hey, I want to talk to the workers
up there on the parapet,
the ones smoking cigarettes
that just jumped back.
You--You're with the American people,
we know that.
But understand,
ask the workers inside,
you're not in
a Federal Government building.
You're in a private Federal Reserve
that uses that name as a fraud.
That'd be like if my first name was
Federal Reserve Jones.
I'm still not
the Federal Government.
I'm not a federal agency.
But, if I said my name was
Federal Reserve,
I could go out
and pay off politicians
and get them to allow me
to get into power
so I could issue
the currency and credit
and then
I could buy up the world.
That's what
these criminals have done.
A lot of people think
that the Federal Reserve
is already
part of the government.
They're not.
It's controlled by cliques of
unelected, unaccountable bankers
meeting in secret.
Most of these people
have never even been through
the formality of a Senate hearing
or a Senate confirmation.
They claim that they're part of
the US government.
They masquerade as if they were part
of the US government.
But in reality,
this is a purely private operation.
Jackals, hyenas, raptors,
all of them loyal,
not to the American people,
but to the Wall Street banks,
which is where most of them come from.
Everyone is pointing
to Barack right now,
President Obama,
and saying,
"Ya gotta get the economy together,
ya gotta get the economy together,"
when in fact,
the President
has very little
to do with the economy.
It's the Federal Reserve Chairman
that at least sets the policy.
That's a privately owned company,
the Federal Reserve Bank.
They set the agenda.
These guys are masquerading
as a federal institution.
They are a
private banking consortium
and this is their front,
their holding company.
The Federal Reserve
is not federal.
It's a front
for a private banking cartel.
That's on record
(congressional testimony),
and they're the ones
orchestrating
the economic collapse
we're seeing right now.
So that's why
we're here.
While at the End the Fed rally
outside the Federal Reserve Bank
in Dallas, Texas, we spoke with
Ron Paul's brother, Wayne Paul.
1913:
The Federal Reserve Act was passed.
Floor of the House, where three members
of Congress were on the floor.
At that time, they only needed
a majority of votes to pass it.
So in 1913,
the Federal Reserve Act was passed.
20 years later, in 1933,
under Roosevelt,
the United States
was declared bankrupt.
And in 1933,
the Federal Reserve private bank says,
"Okay, USA, what are
you gonna pledge as collateral
on the debt
you owe me?"
What happened by 1936?
- Does anybody know?
- They had us...
We instituted Social Security system,
and you and I, and our children,
and our children's children
were pledged as collateral
on the debt of our government
to the Federal Reserve.
And that's
where we're at today.
It took 20 years
to make this country bankrupt
and since then,
our government
has operated under
emergency powers
of our government.
It is not the President
that makes the decision in this country.
It's the Secretary of Treasury
who turns around
and is put in there
by the Federal Reserve
to manage the bankruptcy.
We've been in bankruptcy
ever since.
So, to print 700 billion dollars
and to give it away,
how do they get
away with it?
The manager of the bankruptcy
is told by the Federal Reserve,
"This is the way to go."
That's where
we're at today.
Yes,
we should point out,
Congressman Ron Paul now has
a huge amount of sponsors
for a bill in
the House of Representatives
to abolish the private Federal Reserve
crime syndicate.
In 1913, the money power of the country
was taken away from the people.
By Constitutional privilege,
it belongs with the Congress,
but it was given up
in the Federal Reserve Act.
The Federal Reserve is no more "federal"
than Federal Express.
But yet,
it has the power
to determine the direction
of use of money in our economy.
If we could
take that power back
and put the Federal Reserve
under Treasury,
we start to be
in a position
of being able
to control monetary policy
on behalf of
the United States people.
The Federal Reserve
is totally private
and Alan Greenspan,
two weeks ago on PBS,
on Lehrer News Hour,
said,
on record that
they are above the law,
the Congress,
the President, everyone.
No court can do anything.
"We run America."
What is the, uh,
proper relationship?
What should be
the proper relationship
between a chairman of the Fed
and a President of the United States?
Well, first of all,
the Federal Reserve
is an independent agency
and that means, basically,
that there is
no other agency of government
which can overrule actions
that we take.
So long as
that is in place,
and there is no evidence
that the administration
or the Congress
or anybody else
is requesting
that we do things
other than what we think
is the appropriate thing,
then what the relationships are
don't frankly matter.
Notice what Greenspan is saying.
Greenspan is saying
the Federal Reserve is beyond the law.
And in reality, they are,
in practice, beyond the law.
Nobody, as far as I know,
has ever audited the Federal Reserve.
One of the first things
we ought to do
when we nationalize
the Fed,
is go in there
and find out the audit.
Who stole money?
Who engaged in corruption?
There's a whole
series of people going back
to Volker, to Greenspan,
to Bernanke, uh, and so forth.
Think of the arrogance!
A private group of banks
that have bankrupted the nation
by design,
so they can repo the country.
A private group of banks
that loaned us our own money back
are telling us
they're above the law.
You are not above the law,
criminals!
No one
is above the law!
is above the law,
and the private Federal Reserve
sure as hell ain't either.
Since the founding
of the Federal Reserve
back under
Woodrow Wilson,
the Federal Reserve
has struck out three times.
They didn't stop
the crash of 1929,
they didn't stop
the banking panic of 1930-1933,
and now
they are the cause
of the derivatives crisis
because they're the ones
who inflicted derivatives
on the world with Alan Greenspan.
Instead of our economy
being about
goods and services and
real products and manufacturing,
it's all about
these guys,
the private Federal Reserve
that masquerades
as a government entity,
who controls the issuance
of currency and credit.
They're the ones that have cut off
the liquidity in the market.
They told us to have
a debt-based economy,
then they cut it off,
once they get us under their thumb
and implode the economy
so they can consolidate it.
That's what
they're doing right now.
I mean, it--it's in their own documents.
It's in their own statements.
They claim,
"Give us unlimited power.
Give us trillions of dollars of the
banker bailout bill."
That's already five trillion dollars,
not $850 billion as they say.
And, and,
"We'll get the economy going."
But they're hoarding the money
and buying up other banks
that aren't part
of the Federal Reserve,
buying up insurance companies,
buying up roads,
infrastructures, media empires,
defense contractors.
What the banks do is
they implode an economy
by cutting off, uh,
credit
and then once
things really fall to a low,
and they know the low
because then they buy everything up,
and start then putting more money
back into the economy,
and then
they build it back up.
So they build us up and then shear us,
build us up and shear us,
and they're getting ready...
All over the world they're always
shearing some country, imploding it.
Comes out in their own
IMF and World Bank documents.
That's just the foreign arm
of the same cartel.
And these are the people who claim to be
the saviors of the economy,
the people who have created
every important crisis
in the past hundred years,
the Federal Reserve.
So, it's illegal, it's unconstitutional,
and it's a failure.
And I think the failure is what
everybody can see right now.
Yeah, what they do is,
they make you think
Clinton's evil
in running things.
Then, oh, Bush'll save us,
and then, oh, Bush was evil.
Now, we'll be saved by
Barack Obama.
But he's just a puppet.
But as we get deeper
into this phase,
when they implode
the economy,
they have all the money
and all the control,
and then... but they also like
to pose as the savior.
So, Obama is meant to be
the savior during the depression
and he'll save us
with a million person
(he said
as big or bigger
than our military)
domestic spy force,
a three million person
environmental spy force.
So giving people these jobs
to be government bureaucrats and spies
to go out
and manage, uh, the other,
you know,
290 something million Americans.
And so this is classical fascism.
The Communists also do it.
Any vertically-integrated,
command-and-control
authoritarian system
does this.
So, they're openly following
what the same group of banks
did in Germany, Russia.
You know, it's in
the Communist Manifesto
to have
a private central bank,
because the private central bankers
actually wrote the ideas
that they had
Marx and Engels put out.
People go, "Well, why would
the banks want communism?"
It doesn't exist.
They rape us.
They consolidate us.
They put us into work brigades.
They make us slaves.
And they say,
"It's a people's paradise!
Look at it!
Boy, you're really doing good!"
And then, they transfer all
the wealth of the nation offshore.
The globalists
are outside all the nations.
That gives them safety,
and they play countries off
against each other.
And so that's what
we're facing and dealing with.
And so they're bringing in
classical hardcore tyranny into the US.
But we have
the Internet.
We've grown our numbers.
The alternative media's
exploded.
That's why
they're trying to move in
to shut down and regulate
and tax the web.
But it's
too late for them.
They're, they're playing
in the 19th century, 20th century rules.
It's the 21st century,
this, the century of resistance
to tyranny.
And so it's gonna be
one hell of a fight,
with the people and
free humanity on one side
and the New World Order
on the other.
And every one of you out there counts,
needs to be involved in this fight
like nothing you've been
involved with before,
because this is
life and death.
Everything depends on
exposing these people.
Everything depends on showing the people
that this is the New World Order,
this is
the criminals.
We're dealing
with the king rats here,
the people that are carrying out
tyranny worldwide.
And, either they fall
or we fall.
Either worldwide darkness
and a new age of tyranny and oppression
with a scientific overlay,
or a new age of liberty and freedom
and a new renaissance.
The choice, the choice
is the people's out there.
Okay, we can tell you
what's going on.
You can check out for yourself
and find out it's true.
But don't wait.
Investigate now.
Get involved now.
Go out there
and reach out now.
We don't have time.
If you're looking for the solution,
look in the mirror.
Look right into the mirror
because you out there
men, women, old,
young, black, white,
it doesn't matter.
It's going to be up to you
if they win
or if liberty succeeds
and the people have a chance
of having any future.
These are
cold-blooded eugenicists.
These are cold-blooded people
who think they're God,
think that they're our masters,
that think that we're animals.
These are the guys that funded
Lenin and Stalin, and Hitler and Mao.
These are the guys (it's all on record)
that bankroll this stuff.
They are hardcore vicious,
and they must be resisted.
Up until about
the Kennedy assassination
and the beginning of the war
in Vietnam,
the United States is
a very powerful engine
for world progress.
It's the assassinations,
the Kennedy assassination
and the others
in the 1960s,
the beginning
of the Vietnam war,
and the beginning
of the absolute domination
of the Wall Street group
over every other interest.
Nobody else counts except
the Wall Street money masters.
That has now made
the United States into,
no longer
a force for progress,
but something very different;
often a force for destruction
in the world.
That doesn't need
to remain that way.
The interest of the American people
is to fight the...
Take your government
back from Wall Street,
and make the United States
a force for progress in the world,
which we easily could do
if we could just break the power
of the people behind Obama.
The main banks
of Europe,
which were started by Adam Weishaupt
and, and Rothschild,
the Banque Nationale de Paris,
The Bank of England, The Bank of Italy,
have all financed
the messianic
and, and war leaders
of the last 200 years.
Napoleon.
Lenin. Stalin.
They backed Adolf Hitler.
They backed
Franklin Delano Roosevelt.
And they are backing,
right now,
Barack Obama.
The banking cartel had established
a beachhead in 1913
through
the Federal Reserve Act.
In 1947, they set up
a parallel Shadow Government
through
the National Security Act.
From '47 on,
the National Security State
began the long process
of absorbing
federal and state bureaucracies,
while at
the same time,
undermining
the constitutional power of Congress
and dominating
the Executive Branch.
By controlling the issuance
of currency and credit,
the private Federal Reserve was able
to buy up most of the Fortune 500.
And if a company wouldn't sell,
the bankers would unleash
federal regulators
to run them out of business.
Private central banks in Europe,
the United States and England
took taxpayer money and loaned it
at over 30% interest
to third world nations.
The bankers would then bribe
the leaders of those countries
not to pay back
the loans.
Their third world puppets
would sign agreements
stating that
when the country defaulted,
the banks would be given all
the natural resources and infrastructure
of the once sovereign lands.
But worst of all,
the countries would pledge
future taxes,
paid by the people, in perpetuity,
as profit to the private banks.
By the year 2000,
there were few nations
that had not fallen to the designs
of the money power.
The globalists were now
ready to start
their final phase
of world government takeover,
the destruction
of the Western nation's economies.
To carry out
their final takeover,
they first removed
banking regulations,
like the Glass-Steagall Act,
in the late 1990s.
This allowed
their front companies
to issue unlimited credit
to the world
and to set up
colossal Ponzi schemes,
the likes of which
the world had never seen.
The scams were advertised
by the controlled corporate media
as completely legitimate.
Because of
the fantastic returns,
private investors,
corporations,
state and local governments,
invested heavily.
They had taken the bait:
hook, line and sinker.
To destroy confidence,
in late 2007,
the bankers themselves
began to badmouth
the scams they had created.
Next, the central bankers cut off
the tsunami of fiat money
that they had been using
to pump up the bubble.
When Congress
and the public
refused to write the finance oligarchs
a blank check,
the bankers began to engage
in financial terrorism.
They said that the world would go
into another great depression
unless their demands were met,
further destroying confidence.
The stock market instantly had
its biggest one day loss in history.
But even that wasn't enough
to force Congress
to capitulate
to the offshore banks.
Senator Inhofe
of Oklahoma,
and Congressman
Brad Sherman of California,
amongst others,
told the world
that the entire Congress
had been threatened
with martial law by the White House
and the Treasury Department
if they didn't pass the so-called
banker bailout bill.
The only way
they can pass this bill
is by creating and sustaining
a panic atmosphere.
That atmosphere
is not justified.
Many of us were told
in private conversations
that if we voted
against this bill,
on Monday
that the sky would fall,
the market would drop two
or three thousand points the first day,
another couple thousand
the second day,
and a few members
were even told
that there would be martial law
in America if we voted "no".
That's what I call fear mongering.
Unjustified.
The final version of the bill
was kept secret from the Congress
until minutes before the vote
on October 3rd, 2008.
The Federal Reserve
had promised total transparency,
that every dime
would be accounted for.
To Democrats and Republicans
who've opposed this plan,
I say,
step up to the plate,
let's do what's right
for the country at this time
because the time to act
is now.
...to prevent
the possibility of a crisis,
turning into
a catastrophe.
After its passage,
the public learned with horror
that the bill
was really a financial coup d'etat
by Wall Street.
The bill didn't just give
700 billion dollars to the banks.
It was a blank check.
And as of
February, 2009,
$9.7 trillion has disappeared
into a black hole.
Within 24 hours
of its passage,
Secretary of Treasury
Henry Paulson said,
they were no longer
going to use the money
to unfreeze the mortgage market
by buying bad debt.
We went to Congress.
Illiquid assets looked like
the way to go.
As the situation worsened,
the facts changed.
I will never apologize
for changing an approach or strategy
when the facts change.
Paulson has,
in the meantime, admitted
that the sub-prime mortgage crisis
is not the cause, really,
of the breakdown of the entire
world banking system
and the bankruptcy of most of the banks
in London and in Wall Street.
He said,
"Oh, we're gonna buy up toxic assets
but we're not going to worry about
sub-prime mortgages."
What he's talking about
is derivatives.
Derivatives are
the center of the crisis.
He went on to say
that where the money going
was a secret.
"I believe that banking institutions
are more dangerous
to our liberties
than standing armies.
If the American people
ever allow private banks
to control the issuance
of their currency,
first by inflation,
then by deflation,
the banks and corporations
that will grow up around the banks
will deprive
the people of all property
until their children
wake up homeless
on the continent
their fathers conquered.
The issuing power
should be taken from the banks
and restored to the people,
to whom it properly belongs."
-- Thomas Jefferson,
third President of the United States.
Secretary Paulson came in
with the Vice President
and Fed Chairman Bernanke
and made all these assurances
that there was absolutely
a critical,
immediate need
to get rid of the corrosive,
derivative products.
You know, all the different names,
for this, em...
you know, ubiquitous, you know, uh,
sub-S retraded credit default swap,
blah, blah, blah, blah,
okay.
But they, they talked about them
as though they knew
what the hell
they were.
You got the money
and you immediately said,
"What items?
What auction?"
Now the Treasury just, just basically
cut that out of the bill.
And what, you know,
what we have here
is a situation
where banks are,
are hoarding the money
that they're getting from the TARP.
They're using the money
to purchase other banks.
And all of a sudden,
the Treasury sent a signal to the banks,
"Forget about it.
We're gonna give you
the money that you want,
and you do
what you want with it."
Unless you direct it specifically,
it's not gonna happen.
I don't think anyone questions,
Mr. Kashkari,
that you're working hard.
Our question is,
"Who are you working for?"
Throughout its passage,
President Bush and Senator Obama
worked in tandem
to get Congress to pass the bill,
without even having time
to read it.
Despite the fact,
that in major polls,
98% of the American people
were against the bill,
the leadership in both parties
were for it.
And I really want
to commend Barack Obama
because as
we were involved in the...
this and that, and
different provisions of the bill
to persuade people,
he really gave them confidence
that this was
the right decision
for the American people,
even though it wasn't,
in our view, a great bill, uh,
for them to vote on.
I want to take
a particular moment
to also thank an individual
who's not here,
and that is Barack Obama,
who made numerous calls,
not only
to all of us,
but to members
of our caucus,
and helped us gather the votes
on the Democratic side
to pass this legislation.
Bankheads then
bragged to the press
that they were hoarding
the bailout money
and using it to buy up
smaller, healthy banks
and insurance companies.
Their plan was working
like a charm.
Next, the central bankers loaned
the Federal Government back
787 billion dollars
of our own money, at interest,
for President Obama's so-called
stimulus package.
And just like the banker bailout,
Congress was given less than an hour
to read the 1,070 page-plus
stimulus bill.
Barack Obama, who had pledged
on the campaign trail
to wait five days before a bill
could be voted on
so that the Congress and the people
could have a chance to read it,
said that the stimulus
was too important
and it had
to be passed
before anybody
could see it or read it,
or the crisis would turn
into a catastrophe.
Doing little, or nothing at all,
will result in even greater deficits,
even greater job loss,
even greater loss of income,
and even
greater loss of confidence.
Those are deficits
that could turn a crisis
into a catastrophe
and I refuse to let that happen.
After its Friday passage,
in gangster fashion,
President Barack Obama
took a four day vacation
and said that
there was no rush to sign it.
The spending bill
was really a takeover bill
designed to further
federalize the States
and to pay off rich donors
that had donated to both parties.
As the world slid
deeper into depression,
the bankers celebrated the fire sale
that they had created.
I believe this, the phrase,
"burdens of the office", is overstated.
Yes, Kelly.
Why me?
Oh, the burdens.
Why did the financial collapse
have to happen on my watch?
It's just pathetic, isn't it,
self-pity?
And I don't believe,
uh...
President-elect Obama
will be full of self-pity.
With their access
to unlimited fiat capital,
they could now buy up
sectors of the world economy
not already
controlled by them.
For over a century,
the Anglo-American establishment
had worked to bring
the world system to this point:
artificially-engineered
global bankruptcy.
In an address
before the Trilateral Commission,
in June of 1991,
David Rockefeller
laid out the elites' ultimate goal.
The supernational sovereignty
of an intellectual elite
and world bankers
is surely preferable
to the national auto-determination
practiced in
the last centuries.
Now that the bankers
were holding the world hostage,
they issued their ultimatum.
The only solution
to restart the global economy
would be to set up
a planetary government
ruled by
a new Bank of The World,
a Bank of The World,
owned and controlled by them.
Suddenly,
hundreds of prominent publications
announced the solution,
the people's only salvation.
Time magazine, in an article titled
The New World Order,
said that the new superbank
would control the world's currencies
and set interest rates
and that the new bank would, quote,
"Knock the heads of bad countries
like the United States."
At a meeting of central bankheads
and finance ministers
dubbed
Bretton Woods II,
the plan for world government
was unveiled
by the very bankers
that had engineered the collapse.
Formerly sovereign countries,
would now pay their taxes
directly
to the banking cartel.
Hundreds
of new carbon taxes,
controlling every facet
of human activity,
would only be
the beginning.
Now, all the elite had to do
was to sell the public
on accepting the final phase
of their takeover,
and it's Obama's job
to sucker the public,
in to standing down,
so the bankers agenda
can move forward unhindered.
Never before in US history
has the media gotten
behind a president,
like they are
behind Obama.
The press has pulled out
all the stops,
bestowing a crown of
infallibility upon Obama,
as the savior
of the people.
The elite are betting everything
they've got on Obama's charisma
and hoping that
he can sell the world
on their program
of tyranny.
Yes, there have been differences
between America and Europe.
No doubt, there will be differences
in the future.
But the burdens of global citizenship
continue to bind us together.
A change of leadership
in Washington
will not
lift this burden.
In this new century,
Americans and Europeans alike,
will be required
to do more, not less.
Partnership and cooperation
among nations is not a choice.
It is the only way.
We've got
to give them a stake
in creating the kind of, uh,
world order
that I think
all of us would like to see.
In truth,
Obama is not simply continuing
George W. Bush's policies.
He is radically
expanding them.
I thank President Bush
for his service to our nation.
This film has documented
the painful fact
that Barack Obama's agenda
is the complete opposite
of what
he has claimed it to be.
Now, we will reveal what Barack Obama
and his controllers' true agenda is.
Number one:
Bring the United States
under the complete
regulatory control
of a private, offshore superbank
known as the Bank of the World.
More than a hundred new taxes
are now being developed
under the umbrella
of curbing greenhouse gases.
The new taxes will be paid directly
to the private bank consortium.
At the producer level,
taxes will be paid
on farm animals' flatulence.
At the consumer level,
there will be carbon taxes
on all forms of meat:
beef, poultry,
pork and fish.
All cars will be fitted
with satellite tracking boxes
that will tax driving
by the mile.
And an added tax will be placed
on all fossil fuels
including motor oil
and natural gas.
All plastic products
will have a carbon tax added.
Outdoor space heaters and fireplaces
are to be taxed.
All electricity
produced by coal-powered plants,
will be taxed.
Under
the cap-and-trade system,
citizens will be forced
to pay taxes
on thousands of products
to private cap-and-trade services
owned by Al Gore
and other elitists.
There will be taxes
on light bulbs, water,
trash pickup,
air travel, train travel.
Bus, ship, medicine, steel production,
mining, clothing, laundry, asphalt,
are just a few of the new taxes
to be levied.
But to truly
transform our economy,
to protect our security
and save our planet
from the ravages
of climate change,
we need to ultimately make
clean, renewable energy.
The profitable
kind of energy.
So I ask this Congress
to send me legislation
that places a market-based cap
on carbon pollution
and drives the production
of more renewable energy in America.
That's what we need.
The notion of
anthropogenic global warming
is a fraud.
In other words,
the idea that
the planet is getting warmer,
and that human activity
is somehow responsible,
is a pseudoscientific fraud.
It's a big lie.
It's a monstrosity.
Remember the Nazis:
They had race science, race hygiene.
They said Aryan blood is different
from any other kind of blood.
This was, of course, idiocy,
a fantastic piece of nonsense.
Today,
we've got something similar.
Global warming
caused by human activity.
And the answer to that is carbon tax,
plus cap-and-trade,
according to the wishes of
Al Gore, Prince Charles,
and basically the entire
world banking community,
the world oligarchy.
What they're trying to do with that
is to perpetuate the current system
where bankers rule the world,
financiers rule the world,
and the rest of us
get the crumbs from the table.
But remember, if you try to put on
cap-and-trade and a global warming,
carbon tax with the idea
that you're gonna save the polar bears,
what you're gonna do is
destroy human society.
You're gonna cause
genocide on a massive scale.
The deaths will be measured
in the hundreds of millions,
and indeed,
in the billions.
Just the idea of global warming
means that there'll be
no development for Africa,
no development for
the poorer parts of Southeast Asia,
and no world economic recovery
of any kind, ever,
in our entire lifetime.
So, it's important
to expose and fight
the pseudoscientific fraud
of global warming.
One more point
about this.
You don't need a climatologist
to know that this stuff is a fraud.
I'm a historian.
I can tell you,
in the last thousand years,
we had a period of
very warm temperatures
called the
Medieval Warm Period,
where all kinds of grapes,
and, uh, semi-tropical stuff
were growing very far
into the Northern Hemisphere.
That was
about 1100, 1200.
It happened to correspond
with an all-time maximum of sunspots.
Right now, we can say that
we're going into another maximum period,
where there'll be
some warming,
but we're well within the limits
of the Medieval Warm Period.
About 1600 to 1650,
there was an ice age
in Northern Europe.
The North Sea
was filled with ice.
The German and Dutch ports
and the English ports
were filled with ice.
That corresponds
to an all-time minimum
of sunspot activity,
the Sprer Minimum
and the Maunder Minimum.
So, this has largely got to do
with solar activity.
We can see that other planets,
not just the Earth,
are warming slightly
as a result of increased solar activity.
But we're well
within the minimum.
So, what the oligarchs claim to be
an open and shut scientific case
is a piece of
pseudoscientific nonsense,
and it should be rejected.
Number two:
The social engineers
are fully aware
that the Obama craze
will wear off quickly,
so they are racing
to put in place
the most oppressive police
state control grid in human history.
20,000 battle-hardened,
regular army troops
are now being deployed to patrol
the streets of the United States.
FEMA is now
building giant camps
in every region
of the country
and the Congress
has introduced bills
like the National Emergency
Centers Act, HR 645,
which merges local governments
and the police,
under federal control.
And as we all know,
that have watched these things,
they're ready
for the riots.
With these detention centers
that are being opened up
around the country,
with state police training
for riot control,
in the event of economic calamity
and food riots,
they know what's going on
and they're prepared for it.
So, people better also
prepare for it themselves.
Anyone that's not prepared
for what's going to happen,
they deserve what they get.
Because there's
enough information out there,
pointing
to the problems.
And they should take
all precautionary actions.
Next, Obama ordered
the Defense Department
to issue
DOD Directive 1404.10,
establishing a one million person
civilian army,
under his control.
Simultaneously,
Obama launched USAService.org.
The new web site deceptively
masquerades as a federal agency
but in reality,
is a recruiting tool,
building a separate,
completely private army,
outside of government that takes orders
directly from Obama's controllers.
Barack Obama has refused to rescind
Presidential Decision Directive 51,
signed by George W. Bush.
The directive plainly states:
the President is a dictator
and that Congress is ceremonial.
We cannot continue
to rely only on our military,
in order to achieve
the national security objectives
that we've set.
We've got to have
a civilian national security force
that's just as powerful,
just as strong, just as well-funded.
President Obama and
his Chief of Staff, Rahm Emanuel,
have repeatedly
stated on the record
that all Americans
below the age of 64,
will be forcibly conscripted
into federal service.
Citizenship is not
an entitlement program.
It comes
with responsibilities.
Everybody somewhere
between the ages of 18-25
will serve three months
of basic training and understanding,
in a kind of civil defense.
Now, it doesn't always
have to be service in uniform.
One of the things that,
if you talk to our generals,
they are desperate for
is a civilian counterpart
to our military forces.
- So is this compulsory, then?
- Well...
You have to, in the sense
that it's required of everybody,
18 to 25,
three months.
And at some point,
at that point, you do it.
Obviously,
I'm not gonna sit here and...
perfect legislation;
we'll work that process through.
You could do it
during a college summer.
- Right. I could do it any time.
- You could do after high school.
If you have a demagogue
with a fanatical mass movement,
a personality cultist,
who is imposing
the program of a group
of extreme bankers
and finance oligarchs, that's fascism.
Obama's transition site, Change.gov,
proclaimed
that middle school and
high school students will be forced
to serve
the Federal Government.
Fascism is gutter up,
streets up:
hooligans, thugs,
fervently idealistic students,
swarming adolescents,
just the kind of thing
you see around Obama.
The way you get a population
to enslave itself,
when the police and the army
are no longer enough to do that.
So I think
that's--that's...
If you're a left liberal, uh,
it's time to open your eyes to that.
All young Americans
between the ages of 18 and 24
will be conscripted into
a paramilitary domestic security force.
If Obama has his way,
adults and seniors will also be forced
into other forms of service
for the betterment of the homeland.
Number three:
Disarming the American people.
Obama operatives
in the Congress
have introduced
more than 10 bills
that would end the Second Amendment
as we know it.
HR-1022 would allow
the new Attorney General, Eric Holder,
the dictatorial power
to ban any gun he wishes at will.
In 2008,
before the Supreme Court,
in the DC gun ban case,
District of Columbia vs. Heller,
Holder argued for the complete
disarmament of the American people
and that only the military
should own firearms.
HR-257 would ban
all youth shooting sports,
including YMCA and Youth Olympic
shooting clubs.
HR-45 would force
all gun owners
to undergo
federal psychological screening,
registration and testing
to keep their firearms.
White House Chief of Staff,
Rahm Emanuel,
has proposed
the extrajudicial banning
of any American
on the fraudulent no-fly list
from owning any firearm.
That is,
if you are on the no-fly list,
because you are known
as maybe a possible terrorist,
you cannot buy
a handgun in America.
Over 25,000 Americans are added
each month to the no-fly list,
which numbers
over a million people
who have not been
charged or convicted of any crime.
It's a case
of mistaken identity
for a five-year-old boy
from Normandy Park.
He had trouble boarding a plane
because someone with his same name
is wanted
by the Federal Government.
KING-5's Mimi Jung is live
at SeaTac Airport to explain.
Mimi...
Laurie, it's hard to believe
that a five-year-old
could be considered a threat,
but that's exactly what happened
here at SeaTac, last week,
when Matthew Gardner
showed up for a flight to LAX.
And they are fighting each other...
As five-year-olds go,
Matthew Gardner
is about as harmless
as you can get.
But when he and his mom checked in
for their flight at SeaTac, last week,
Matthew was considered
the criminal.
If you're on
that no-fly list,
your access to the right
to bear arms is canceled,
because you're not
part of the American family.
You don't deserve
that right.
There is no right for you,
if you're on that terrorist list.
And even though this Matthew Gardner
is only in kindergarten,
TSA workers still conducted
a full-blown search.
They searched
all of our belongings.
They took everything apart,
piece-by-piece.
Nadia Counter says
it wasn't easy being treated
as a possible threat
to national security.
I picked up my child to give him a hug
and tell him, you know,
"It's okay,
we're doing fine,"
and they reported to me
that I was not allowed to touch him,
he was
a security risk,
and they had to re-search me
to make sure that
I had not obtained
any materials from him.
Number four:
Massive restrictions on
the First Amendment guarantee
of free speech.
The President, Congress, and the FCC,
have announced plans
to not only curtail speech
on talk radio and newspapers,
but to also regulate speech
on the Internet,
through the Orwellian named
Fairness Doctrine.
The Obama machine
is also pressuring Congress
to pass draconian
hate speech laws
that will eviscerate
the First Amendment.
Number five:
They plan to further
federalize healthcare
so that the government
can dictate
what kind of care
citizens receive.
Modeled after the British System,
this includes rationing care
and restricting
what procedures
the handicapped and elderly
are eligible for.
Number six:
Obama
is already pushing
to expand the Department
of Defense budget
and to station more US troops overseas
to encircle Russia, China, Iran;
as well as setting up bases in Africa,
under the pretext of humanitarian aid,
and dominate and occupy Africa
through AFRICOM.
So we're taking
your phone calls,
seeing what you think of
Barack H. Obama.
Is he a Judas goat?
Is he a front man? Is he a betrayer?
Let's go to Anthony
in Georgia.
Anthony, what's your take
on Barack Obama?
They put the face of Barack Obama
as part of their public relations
because it's like the old folk tales
about vampires.
A vampire cannot force his way
into somebody's house.
It's against some kind
of metaphysical law.
So, the vampire has to persuade
the resident of the household
to open the door
and invite him in.
So, they're gonna look at the people,
at Barack Obama,
which looks like them
and appears to be on their side.
They're gonna say,
"Okay, here's my ally,
let me open the door
and let me let, uh,
this person in."
And then, Barack Obama,
who's just, of course,
a front man
for the American Empire,
where he's gonna have
the entire US Navy,
the entire US Army,
and the entire US Marines,
under AFRICOM Command.
And, of course,
he's gonna turn it into a new Iraq
and he's gonna turn it
into a new Afghanistan.
Everything,
every operation that you see
going on in
Iraq and Afghanistan,
is going to propagate
to the poor countries of Africa.
- And, it's a shame.
- Well sir, sir, I agree with you.
Sir, I agree with you.
They're looking
to the people,
they see
a handsome, smiling African face.
You know, he's all,
"Hey, I'm from Kenya."
And then,
it's a total bait-and-switch.
But it's the same thing here
in the United States,
where they
would get... sellout...
Native American Chiefs
to sell out their people.
- This is the oldest trick in the book.
- Right.
And he can also pacify
the most downtrodden minority groups
in the United States.
So he's saying,
"Hey, get ready for sacrifice.
Get ready to lose
your standard of living."
They're like,
"Yeah, I love Obama."
They could never get away with this
with a John McCain.
Obama basically does
a couple of things.
One is, again, this idea:
Kick the Chinese out of Africa.
Kick them out of Sudan
where they get oil.
Kick them out of Zimbabwe
were they get raw materials.
Start a civil war in Congo,
another big source of raw materials.
Al-Qaeda, an arm of
the US intelligence community,
is now active in
Algeria, Tunisia, Morocco.
You've got a destabilization going on
in Kenya, around Odinga.
That's Obama's cousin.
This is a guy
who has two children.
They're Obama's niece and, well,
nephew, in a broad sense,
and one of them is named Raoul
and the other one is named Winnie,
after Winnie Mandela
who did the necklacing
and political assassinations
in South Africa.
So this Odinga is essentially
a CIA destabilizing operation in Kenya.
And he's got a Odinga Islamic Alliance
to crush the Christians in Kenya.
But this also reaches
into Ethiopia.
It reaches into
Uganda, Congo, Tanzania,
and a whole bunch
of other countries in that region.
So, all of Africa
is a battlefield in flames,
between the US
and the Chinese,
with Obama leading the charge
to kick the Chinese out
for geopolitical reasons.
Number seven:
Radically expand federal control
over family farms and ranches
through the animal ID
and premises ID system.
Number eight:
Accelerate the merger
of the United States
with Canada and Mexico,
under the Security
and Prosperity Partnership.
He is also accelerating the transfer
of remaining federal authority
to unelected quasi-governmental bodies
like the World Trade Organization.
Number nine:
Obama must convincingly play
the part of the President
and convince the people
of the United States
that the buck actually
stops with him.
This is critical
to the globalist master plan,
because in 4 to 8 years,
Obama must take the blame,
as Bush did,
for the New World Order's
horrific agenda.
At that point, the elite will put
a new puppet
in the ceremonial seat
of power
and build him up as the savior,
only to tear them down again.
And so the process is repeated,
over and over.
For their program
to work,
it is essential
that the people not learn
that the presidency is now
nothing more than theater.
Because if they did,
the people would stop looking
at the pawns,
and start looking
for the king.
Through this system of deceit,
the elites' criminal agenda
can continue forever
because the people waste
all of their political energy,
debating the media spectacle,
instead of investigating
the globalist agenda.
Number ten:
It's Obama's job
to sell the public
on globalist policies
that aren't in
the people's best interest.
But the overlords
have many salesmen.
His most important function
is to protect the criminal oligarchs
from prosecution
while they loot
the economy worldwide,
start new wars,
and engage in torture.
They're called
Generation O
and they were the key
to Barack Obama's White House win.
Yes we can, can, can.
During the campaign,
Barack Obama used the Internet,
like no other candidate
before him,
harnessing the energy of millions
of his supporters.
But the question now is,
what to do with this young,
eager, energetic army.
This gives Barack Obama
and his administration
contact information
for so many people.
So, next time,
he needs to push his legislation,
he can contact
all these people.
Kennedy-esque.
I feel as though this was like
when John F. Kennedy was elected.
Shouting, smiles,
and tears.
Oh, my God!
This is the best day of my life.
It was the scope of Obama's victory
that was most impressive.
I saw a photograph
of Obama playing basketball.
And I said,
"You know what?
I see him as a leader,
and that's the world
that's in his hands."
Own a piece of history,
commemorating the day
the world changed forever.
His confident smile and kind eyes
are an inspiration to us all.
In summation, Barack Obama
is a Madison Avenue-created fad.
All of
the crazed Obama worship
being pushed
by the corporate media
is scientifically designed
to capture the public
in a net of peer-pressure
mass euphoria.
If the New World Order
can just distract the public
for a few more years,
the elite can finish constructing
their police state control grid.
Now, a lot of times,
we don't want to know the issue.
Right.
We don't want
to know the issue.
We feel...
What do you call
this thing
where you get this false sense
of gratification,
but because a black man is in office,
everything's goin' be alright?
No, everything's
not goin' be all right.
Yeah.
Until you look into the agenda
on what the Democratic Party
has been about, is about,
and will be about,
regardless if Barack Obama's
the president or not.
And that's real.
Barack Obama
is the perfect Trojan horse.
He makes the people feel like
they finally have a place at the table,
even as he betrays them.
I won't have to worry about
paying my mortgage.
Oh, it's such a blessing to see you,
Mr. President.
Thank you for taking time
out of your day.
Never, in my life, would think
that this would ever happen.
Sadly, many Obama supporters can't see
what's right in front of their faces
because they've already invested
their very identity
in this artificially-created
cult movement.
Throughout history,
it has happened over and over again.
People turn their intellect
over to cult-of-personality
mass movements,
and it's happening again.
The evidence presented
in this film is documented fact,
and those that ignore
what history has taught us,
do so
at the peril of us all.
As frightening as the information
in this film is,
there are many things
we can do
to stop the globalist agenda
dead in its tracks.
First, we expose the cult of Obama
for what it is:
A sad hoax.
Next, realize that we are
all being propagandized, 24/7.
Investigate all information
for yourself;
be it political parties,
the media, or this film.
Be aware of the tricks
that the elite use,
like the staging of false-flag terror attacks
and other crises.
Rediscover the Constitution
and Bill of Rights.
Promote a culture
of true liberty.
There is a reason
the internationalists
are attempting to destroy
the sovereignty of all 50 states.
They know it is
one of the biggest threats
to their domination.
The Federal Government
has been completely hijacked
by foreign interests,
and more than 25 states,
have recognized this fact and are moving
to block the New World Order,
at the state level by declaring
their Tenth Amendment powers.
But most important of all,
there is a huge awakening
taking place in the United States
and across the world
against the globalist agenda.
Free people everywhere
are joining together
in saying "No"
to corruption and tyranny,
and "No"
to world government.
This is the center of endurance,
and endurance is what wins wars.
Not how many people you kill,
but how long can you endure.
George Washington lost
almost every battle he had,
but he endured!
He out-endured the British.
And that's how the battle was won:
Endurance.
And each and every one of you
watching this,
every single
one of you,
is just as important as the people
who were our founding fathers.
As... that you are
just as important
as the Sons of Liberty
who met in the 1770s
to--to philosophize about freedom,
to philosophize about a republic,
to philosophize
about a truly free country
with a republic.
There's a billion people
on the planet.
It only take one
to change it.
Are you the one?
There may be everybody
in your classroom bugging out.
Your whole school
may be on fire,
with kids,
wild and bringing guns there.
But are you the one?
Nature has
a way of abundance.
Nature puts out a lot of stuff,
looking for the one!
So, if you're gonna go along
with the trend of,
"Let's just kill each other,
let's disrespect each other,"
then you're part
of Nature's plan, as well,
to be part of, just the,
the, the, the excess.
But if you think more of yourself
than just being the excess,
you'll do
more for yourself.
Are you The One?
Everybody's
not gonna make it,
but you have an opportunity
to save yourself.
Well, we don't have to look back
thousands or even hundreds of years
to see how dangerous
this present-day situation is.
We can look back
to Bolshevik Russia.
We can see the takeover
by the Bolsheviks,
talking about
the people's revolution,
the positive change.
And Lenin came in
and then Stalin.
The fact is, is that
over forty million Russians,
between
1925 and 1940,
good Russians,
people who were Christians,
people who had,
who had their own businesses,
people who were educated;
they were exterminated,
because they had their own business,
because they were educated,
because they believed,
believed in God's law.
We can look over
at Germany.
Germany was in a very,
very terrible economic situation
and this very charismatic leader
called Adolf Hitler comes in.
He, he, he makes
the roads good
and he promises a better life
for the people,
and within 10 years,
you see a completely
nationalized, centralized,
dictatorial situation,
where millions and millions of people
were exterminated.
And then we can go
to Maoist China.
Mao came in.
He, he, promised change,
he promised a better life,
and within five years,
sixty million Chinese were exterminated.
They don't teach that,
they don't teach that
in the schools
these days,
and it wasn't that
long ago.
And I pray, pray,
pray to God
that this will not happen
in the United States.
And the way it won't happen,
is if you, and your friends,
and all of us together,
take action to say, "No".
This country is too precious.
It's too wonderful.
It--it's too good of a place
to lay down as a victim.
Greatness could arise,
once we break the shackles
of the government
that's holding us back.
One thing America has
more than any other country
is an entrepreneurial spirit.
One thing we have
more than any other country
is the ability
to be innovators.
You know,
if I was born in Italy,
I wouldn't be the trend forecaster
I am today
because I would've been
locked into a culture
of thinking one way.
We have that
freedom of expression
and freedom of thought
that could free us
to create greatness again,
if, if Big Brother
doesn't come down on us harder.
Humankind
is at a historic crossroads.
The forces of globalism
are marching towards
absolute despotism.
Look in the mirror.
Count the cost.
And decide:
Are you going to let
history repeat itself?
Or, will you stand tall
with freedom lovers everywhere
and stop the completion
of a world dictatorship?
Transcript: CitizenDoctor
[Alex Jones Movie Translation Project]
Final Edits by: VeRdiKT
[SubScene.com]
If you're a translator,
please help us translate this movie...
Go to http://tinyurl.com/AJonesSRT!